[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the total budget of Nepal for the Fiscal Year 2081/82?",
    "answer": "19 Kharba,64 Arba, 11 Karod"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "How many parts, articles and schedules are there in Nepal’s constitution 2072?",
    "answer": "35 parts, 308 articles and 98 schedules"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the full from of SIM as used in Mobile phone?",
    "answer": "Subscriber identification modules"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the height of Kanchanjunga Himal, the second highest Himalaya of Nepal? Say the height in meters.",
    "answer": "8586m"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Name the lone survivor of the Saurya Airlines crash of July 24, 2024 that occurred during take-off at the TIA airport, killing 18 people on board.",
    "answer": "Captain Manish Ratna Shakya"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "नेपालमा रहेका ७५३ वटा स्थानीय तहमा कुल वडा संख्या कति छ ?",
    "answer": "6743 वटा वडा"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "बौद्ध धर्मका चार धाम भनेर कुन कुन ठाउँलाई चिनिन्छ ?",
    "answer": "लुम्बिनी, बोध गया, सारनाथ, कुशीनगर"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "सार्वजनिक ५ पटक विश्वकप फुटबल जित्ने राष्ट्र, ब्राजिलले सो उपाधि कुन कुन वर्षहरुमा जितेको थियो ?",
    "answer": "सन् 1958, 1962, 1970, 1994, 2002"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "प्रसिद्ध ग्रन्थ महाभारत अनुसार महाभारत युद्धमा धृतराष्ट्रका पुत्र कौरवहरु मध्ये बाँचेका एक मात्र पुत्र को थिए ?",
    "answer": "युयुत्सु"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is the mass in grams of one cubic centimeter of water?",
    "answer": "1gm"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "One trillion is 1 followed by 12 Zeros, what is 1 followed by 18 zeros?",
    "answer": "One quintillion"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "विश्व खुशि सुचकांक 2025 मा नेपालको स्थान कति रहेको छ ?",
    "answer": "121 औं स्थान"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "भ्वाइस अफ नेपाल सिजन ६को बिजेता को हुन् ?",
    "answer": "प्रोसेस पाण्डे"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "विश्वका सबैभन्दा अग्लो स्थानमा रहेका झरना कुन हो र यो कुन देशमा  रहेको छ ?",
    "answer": "एन्जल , भेनेजुएला"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "त्रिभुवन विश्वविद्यालयका वर्तमान उपकुलपति को हुन्?",
    "answer": "प्रा.डा. दीपक अर्याल"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "Credit Crunch भन्नाले के बुझिन्छ ?",
    "answer": "वित्तीय प्रणालीमा लगानिमा योग्य पूँजीको अभाव"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "प्रसिद्ध Hyundai motor company कुन देशको उत्पादन् हो ?",
    "answer": "South Korea"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Who won the madan puraskar in the year 2080 BS and what is the title of book?",
    "answer": "Mohan Mainali, Mukam Ranamaidan"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "In which municipality is the Dailekh petroleum site located?",
    "answer": "Bhairavi Rural municipality"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Which Nepali climber ascended all 14 peaks above 8000 meters within 8 months?",
    "answer": "Kami Sherpa"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "Which goal is known as the Hand of God? Say the name of match, scorer and opponent team",
    "answer": "1986 worldcup quarter final, Diego Maradona, England"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What was the name of the operation of Israel latest attack on Iran?",
    "answer": "Operation Rising Lion"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "Name the director of the famous documentary “Honey Hunters of Nepal”",
    "answer": "Eric Valli"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "Which is the first highway of Nepal?",
    "answer": "Tribhuvan Rajpath"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What was the name of the first computer virus?",
    "answer": "Creeper"
  }
]
